{
    "id": "034c6b7a26c64fd98bf25486c0ff7326",
    "title": "Few and little exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "8ceff0513b7a43408329b7429c9b6c1e",
            "title": "Few, Little, The Few, The Little",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "…………………. children participated in the program.",
                    "description": "We use few with countable nouns and little with uncountable nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "A little",
                        "Few",
                        "Little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There is ………………… water in the well.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The average MP has ………………….. real power.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "His ideas are difficult. ………………… people can understand them.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Few",
                        "Little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have gotten a ..................... meat and a ………………….. eggs.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "little, few",
                        "few, little",
                        "few, few",
                        "little, little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can I try ………………….. of your soup?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "little",
                        "a little",
                        "few",
                        "a few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "In spite of being the daughter of a politician, she has ………………… interest in politics.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "little",
                        "a few",
                        "a little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Money is of ………………….. consequence.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "few",
                        "little",
                        "a little"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We were given ………………. work today than yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "little",
                        "fewer"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He earns ……………….. money than his wife.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "less",
                        "little",
                        "few"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}